<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi (Imam Mehdi)</title>
    <link>https://gohar-shahi.com</link>
    <description>Introduction of Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi and His Teachings</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 09:08:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://gohar-shahi.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <generator>Python RSS Generator</generator>
    <item>
      <title>
      Younus AlGohar books | Dastoor e Riaz ,Rukhsar e Riaz , Devan e Shahi | Nisab e Mehdi , Malfuzat e Mehdi and Imam al Mubeen
    </title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/younus-algohar-books</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Deen Ilahi in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:07:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/younus-algohar-books</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
      Deen e Ilahi | Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi Books Deen e Ilaahi (Religion Of God) in pdf
    </title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books</link>
      <description>Download  Deen Ilahi , Ishwar Dharma, Religion Of God, Khuda ka Deen , Deen e Ilahi Pashtu, Deen e Ilahi Farsi, Deen e Ilahi assamese, Deen e Ilahi Bangla Authored By Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
      Here Are Some Articles Providing More Details and Answering Common
      Questions About His Divine Eminence Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi
    </title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/More</link>
      <description> Discover a collection of articles that delve deeper into the life,
      teachings, and mission of His Divine Eminence Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi.
      These articles address frequently asked questions, providing clarity
      on His spiritual philosophy, the concept of divine love, and the
      global impact of His message.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 18:18:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/More</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gohar Shahi | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/gohar-shahi</link>
      <description>His Divine Eminence Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi is a revered spiritual
      leader, author, and founder of Messiah Foundation International. He is
      regarded by many as the Awaited Imam Mehdi, Promised Messiah, and
      Kalki Avatar.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 18:14:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/gohar-shahi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
      Gohar Shahi Images on moon | Imam Mehdi images on Moon | gohar-shahi.com
    </title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/gohar-shahi-images-on-moon</link>
      <description>100+ Imam Mehdi Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi images on Moon , Divine Signs of God </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 18:13:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/gohar-shahi-images-on-moon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Younus AlGohar | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/about-younus-algohar</link>
      <description>Younus AlGohar is a only  official Representative of Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi , He is in charge of spreading the divine mision of love of God to evey soul. He is Also founder of Mehdi Foundation International.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 18:11:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/about-younus-algohar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is Gohar Shahi ? | about Gohar Shahi | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/who-is-gohar-shahi</link>
      <description>  His Divine Eminence Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi is a revered spiritual
      leader, author, and founder of Messiah Foundation International. He is
      regarded by many as the Awaited Imam Mehdi, Promised Messiah, and
      Kalki Avatar.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 23:49:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/who-is-gohar-shahi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disappearnce of His Divine Eminence Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/disappearence</link>
      <description>His Holiness Riaz Ahmed revealed in His presence that He would disappear for some time and later reappear in this world alongside Jesus Christ. This return is destined to counter the satanic powers and reconnect humanity with God through the teachings of love and heart awakening.
In anticipation of His disappearance, His Holiness appointed Younus AlGohar as His Divine Eminence's Representative. He declared, Whoever wishes to meet Gohar Shahi (Himself) should meet Younus AlGohar. This appointment was a clear directive to ensure the continuation of His divine mission.
Despite the explicit instructions and foreknowledge provided by His Holiness about His disappearance, certain individuals, including His sons and some family members, falsely declared Him dead. They constructed a tomb in His name and began collecting money from followers, exploiting His Holiness's legacy for personal gain.  
Today, His Holiness's sacred mission is under the guidance and supervision of Younus AlGohar through the establishment of a new organization, Messiah Foundation International. This organization is dedicated to preserving and spreading the true teachings and mission of His Holiness Riaz Ahmed.
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 23:33:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/disappearence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rohani safar book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/rohani-safar-by-gohar-shahi</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Rohaani Safar in pdf | gohar-shahi.com</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:56:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/rohani-safar-by-gohar-shahi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
      List of Some Videos in which His Holliness Gohar Shahi teaches the love of
      God to ordinary people
    </title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/Videos</link>
      <description>His Holliness Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi went to Mosques, Mandars(Hindu Temples), Churches, Gurdwara(Sikhism Worship place) and gave lectures to Thousand of People there. His Hollines broke all walls of Religions and taught all the humaity one Leason Love Of God . According to His Hollines GOHAR SHAHI love of God is the Extract of Every Religion, Without it Religion is useless. You would find this same Lesson in every video, book, speak of Gohar Shahi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:51:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/Videos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gohar Shahi Gallery</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/gallery</link>
      <description>150+ images of Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi , see and download freely</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:47:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/gallery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where is Gohar Shahi now | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/where-is-gohar-shahi-now</link>
      <description>  His Divine Eminence Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi is a revered spiritual
      leader, author, and founder of Messiah Foundation International. He is
      regarded by many as the Awaited Imam Mehdi, Promised Messiah, and
      Kalki Avatar.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 14:07:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/where-is-gohar-shahi-now</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi Biography</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/life</link>
      <description>His Holiness Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi graced this earth on 25 November 1941. His Hollines Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi belongs to a village of Pakistan Dhok Gohar Shah which is located in City of Gujar khan, district Rawalpindi , province Punjab. His Hollines Real name is Riaz Ahmed and the suffix Gohar Shahi is from your family backgrounds.He is a fifth generation descendant of the Sufi Baba Gohar Ali Shah.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 13:45:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/life</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
      Manifestation of His Hollines Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi Images in the Moon,
      Mars, and various other planets
    </title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/insight</link>
      <description>Jesus Christ is symbolic to divinity, a towering personality, and enjoys a close relationship to God, hence, needs no formal introduction at all. His fame stands out. Images of Jesus Christ have appeared on many planets and locations. Many individuals of the present era are fortunate enough to have met Jesus Christ in person. His Divine Eminence Ra Gohar Shahi is also present on earth. His Divine Eminence is always on the move, and does not stay in one specific home. The images of His Divine Eminence are prominent on various planets including Mars. His Divine Eminence has penned some remarkable books on spirituality, which are available at www.goharshahi.com. His Divine Eminence Ra Gohar Shahi comes from Pakistan, and advocates spiritual sciences and Sufism.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 13:39:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/insight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Jashan-e-Shahi and the Reasons Why it is Celebrated?</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/jashnshahi</link>
      <description>On the 15th of Ramadan 1977, a series of unique secretive conversations (Ilhaamat or inspiration) with God also began. The promise of ‘Radhiya Mardhiya’ (‘Your will is my will, my will is your will’) took place and rank was also granted. Since every rank (martaba) and ascension (meraaj) is related to the 15th of Ramadan, this is why in order to express feelings of happiness and thanksgiving, Jashan-e-Shahi is celebrated every year.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 13:31:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/jashnshahi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
      Some selected features of His Divine Eminence Ra Gohar Shahi's esoteric
      personality
    </title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/somefeatures</link>
      <description>God deployed one of His sub-spirits (Jussa-e-Tawfeeq-e-Ilahi) with His Divine Eminence Gohar Shahi at the age of 19, which stayed with His Divine Eminence for a year and under the influence of which, His Divine Eminence tore away His clothes, and went into the jungle of Jam Dataar with a piece of cloth wrapped around his body. The presence of the sub- spirit of God with His Divine Eminence was but temporary yet, and it would be absent for the following 14 years. In the year 1975, the same divine sub-spirit was the reason for His Divine Eminence’s retreat in the jungle of Sehwan.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 13:26:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/somefeatures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi Teachings</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/Teaching</link>
      <description>Teachings of Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi are profound, unique, and straightforward. The essence of his message is: Awaken your heart's spirit and connect with God through it. When the heart chants the name of God, God’s love automatically enters the heart, filling it with divine light and serenity.
    As the heartbeats get prominent, try to synchronise ‘Allah Allah’ with every beat or ‘Allah’ with one heartbeat and ‘Hu’ with the other. Place your hand on the heart sometimes, feel your heartbeats and try to synchronise the name ‘Allah’. Occasionally, synchronise ‘Allah’ with the pace of the pulse. Imagine the word ‘Allah’ is entering your heart. Dhikr (chanting) of ‘Allah-Hu’ is better and more effective than that of Dhikr-Allah. Those reluctant and afraid of ‘Hu’, instead of deprivation, they might as well synchronise just ‘Allah’ in their heartbeats. People of Dhakuriyah (science of God’s remembrance), and Wird-o-Wadhaif (verbal chanting with the rosary) ought to stay as clean as possible.
    </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 13:24:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/Teaching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
      The Return of Jesus: Jesus Christ meets Gohar Shahi in America
    </title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/jesusreturn</link>
      <description>On 29th May 1997, I was at the El Monte Lodge in Taos, New Mexico. During the second half of the night, I felt the presence of a man in my room. There was not enough light, so at first I thought it was one of my followers.I asked him, ‘Why have you come?’ the man replied, ‘I have come to see you.’ I turned on the light and I saw a handsome young man standing before me, whom I did not know. Seeing him, I felt immense energy and spiritual ecstasy in my soul and spiritual entities, a similar spiritual ecstasy that I would feel and experience in the gathering of the ‘Higher Realms’.
    I learnt that he could speak many languages. The young man told me, ‘I am Jesus (Son of Mary); I am in America, presently.’ I asked him, ‘Where do you live?’ he replied, ‘I neither had a home in the past nor now.’</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 13:22:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/articles/jesusreturn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deen Ilahi Assamese book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-assamese</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Deen Ilahi Assamese  in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:59:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-assamese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deen Ilahi Bangla book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-bangla</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Deen Ilahi Bangla  in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:59:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-bangla</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deen Ilahi farsi book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-farsi</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Deen Ilahi farsi  in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:59:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-farsi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deen Ilahi Hindi book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-hindi</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Deen Ilahi Hindi in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:59:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-hindi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deen Ilahi Kashmiri book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-kashmiri</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Deen Ilahi Hindi in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:59:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-kashmiri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deen Ilahi Malayalam book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-malayalam</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Deen Ilahi Malayalam  in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:58:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-malayalam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deen Ilahi Marathi book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-marathi</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book religion of God  in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:58:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-marathi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deen Ilahi pashto book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-pashto</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Deen Ilahi pashtu  in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:58:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-pashto</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deen Ilahi punjabi book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-punjabi</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Deen Ilahi Assamese  in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:58:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-punjabi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deen Ilahi Tamil book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-tamil</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Deen Ilahi Tamil in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:58:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi-tamil</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deen Ilahi book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book Deen Ilahi in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:57:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/deen-ilahi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Religion of God book | gohar-shahi.com</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/books/religion-of-god</link>
      <description>Riaz Ahmed Gohar Shahi book religion of God  in pdf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:56:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/books/religion-of-god</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gohar Shahi App</title>
      <link>https://gohar-shahi.com/app</link>
      <description>Discover the life, teachings, and books of Ra Gohar Shahi through this beautiful offline app.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:42:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://gohar-shahi.com/app</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>